Team Setti Dragons Bull Sacramento Notebook
I am Waka Yasumori, from Iginari Tohoku.
Please.
Start of the second part.
It's not really decided. To speak.
That's right.
But he told me before we went around that he had something he wanted to ask me.
He's a very heavenly person.
Is that so?
Surprising.
I've been watching your Instagram, and I know you love Japanese sweets.
They always look so delicious.
So you like Japanese sweets too?
I like them a lot.
I see.
Both Western and Japanese?
I love both Western and Japanese sweets, and I want you to make the best Japanese sweets for me.
What? Can you go for a lump of sugar?
Yes, I can. Yes, I do.
Well, there's a really good one at Rakuiwa.
Rakuiwa?
Raku-iwa, you know, for altars and stuff like that.
It's beautiful.
Flower patterns.
Colorful ones. They come in little boxes like this.
They are made of sugar, but they use different kinds of sugar.
They use different kinds of sugar, but they use different kinds of sugar, and they dissolve in the mouth differently.
Some of them get stuck in your teeth.
Some get stuck in your teeth, and others just melt in your mouth.
I prefer the light ones that melt in my mouth.
There are white ones and red ones that are just circles.
Oh, yeah. They don't look good. There was a red and white one that didn't show up.
I forgot the name of it, but I'll send it to you.
Thank you very much.
It's probably the ultimate sweet-sugar thing.
It might not be as interesting. Maybe not interesting, texture-wise.
But I'm happy.
There's no development, it's just sweet.
I'm happy.
Really?
I'm really in trouble.
Not at all.
I thought I was going to get diabetes.
I really like sugar.
You should go for a checkup. Every year.
That's really true, isn't it?
It's really dangerous.
That's right.
Be careful.
It's not good.
It's not safe. Because there's a gal out there.
It's coming out with this hand.
It comes out naturally.
That's right.
I've been recommending it lately. Is there anything you're into?
You know how you put all the highlights together?
I've watched it a lot.
Really?
I've been wanting to eat it.
I'm sure there are places like that in Tohoku. I love those kinds of restaurants.
I love it.
Kagibutsuki.
It's really delicious.
Want some?
Kagibutsuki is a gift.
We don't always buy them.
That's true.
It's like a souvenir.
Do you like sweets?
I do. That's fine. Let's talk like that.
Yes, I do.
You like bread?
I do.
There is a bread in Fukushima called Cream Box.
There is a bread called "Cream Box" in Fukushima, and it has a thick cream on top of the bread, like a mixture of condensed milk and milk.
It looks delicious.
It's really good. I love it.
I also bake toast at home. I pour condensed milk on it.
And I put sugar on it too.
It's great.
So I think I like it a lot.
It's so delicious.
Romeo's 30,000 Tree's cream boxes are sold at Sendai Station and other places.
It's such a famous thing.
It's like the food of Fukushima, and it's famous, and it's really delicious.
I'll tell Yuna.
I'll probably go get some.
I'll get some for Kagi's favorite too.
I see.
It's really good.
I've heard good things about it.
But I haven't had a chance to visit Tohoku recently.
Maybe if we could do a concert together, we could go?
I did.
Can I join you?
I did.I did.
But it would be nice to have at least an opening act.
That's fine. Let's get that part right. Now.
An opening act is good.
We do a 15-minute opening act, see a live performance from Tohoku, and have a meal.
And then have dinner.
That's great. But I want to do it.
I did a choco-sauce live show with Basho the other day.
Next time, we'll do Nagoya and Sendai.
It would be nice to do it with participants. Including Basho.
Sure, that's a good idea.
But I want to go to the North Sea region and Taiwan.
Where would you like to go? If not Taiwan.
We can go next time. If you don't mind going anywhere.
I used to go to Hawaii.
That's right.
I'd like to go to the ocean, or the North and South Pole.
I want to go to the ocean, don't you?
I'd like to go.
I don't know if I can go.
But, I mean, if we go to Hawaii or something, won't our schedule be packed? Again.
But they let me do some sightseeing, so I can go to Tokyo, but they are the type to take care of the countryside.
He said Tokyo is fine.
Yes, yes. Tokyo is already in Tokyo.
Tokyo is a place to work.
Let's go home soon.
I see. Then we'll have to go to Hawaii.
I want to go.
I want to go, don't you?
I want to go. It's definitely fun.
Here comes the question.
What do you like about being a regional group? I think it's Lou.
But I think it's kind of laid-back. In a good way. Because they are laid-back.
That's true.
But also, when you go to a local gummy bear, you can feel it, you can feel the same feeling.
That's why I feel very comfortable.
Even though there are a lot of idols gathered at Staples.
Wow! It seems so local.
Don't you think so?
I think so.
I know. I can see why.
So, it's something.
So, you think Tokyo Gumi is really strong.
Like, it looks strong.
I don't know how to describe it.
I can feel its soul. Local gummy bears.
There's a sense of looseness about the local products.
There is a sense of security.
That's for sure.
Also, isn't it great to have a hometown?
It's a big deal.
It's a big thing to have a separate place to return to, separate from Tokyo.
That's for sure.
Do you have any questions?
If you could switch groups, what would you do?
Did you have a moment when you thought it would be tiring?
It might be tiring. There has always been a tendency to say, "It's tiring, but as long as you work hard, you'll be fine.
As long as you work hard, you'll be fine.
There are so many exciting songs, it's amazing.
But what I've always wanted to do is shampoo heart.
I want to play Shampoo Heart.
I love it.
It's okay, it's okay. Do it.
I'm so happy.
Do it.
I've always loved you.
I want you to do it. Come on in, come on in.
This one. But that song might be popular.
I really like Nie Kawada's music.
When I heard it for the first time, I was so surprised, and if people knew it was Nie Kawada's song, they would be like, "Oh!
I was like, "Oh, wow!
I'm so happy.
What's my name?
Uchiirato.
I really want to do that.
It's definitely fun.
But I can't move formations.
There are too many people and I can't remember the numbers.
I just use that phrase all the time.
I want to do this because I can stay wherever I want.
It's totally fine.
I want to do that. It's fun.
There are nine of us, so we have to move around in formation a lot.
It was really dizzying to see them move around.
It was like we were moving from one place to another all the time.
Are you the type of person who can remember numbers? Relatively.
I'm the type that can do it.
Who often gets the numbers wrong?
We are donkeys.
We are overwhelmingly Donki.
I've always been a donkey.
I say 0.5, but it's more like 0.25.
I see.
There are times when I simply make a mistake.
But it depends on the song.
Surprisingly, there are not so many people who make mistakes. I don't care about mistakes.
I'm the type of person who doesn't care much about mistakes.
That's no good.
What do you mean?
Maybe they're saying it about me.
I see. Depends on who's looking.I see. It depends on the viewer.
I think it's more about fun and being seen.
But of course, I also pay attention to the number.
I don't think it's so much about the number as it is about the tension.
I try not to worry too much about that when it comes to the members.
Then maybe it's the same.
We were also told to do our best because of the position of the lights.
He pointed at us. They said, "This is the place, come here.
The lighting crew was still working on it, but they would often go to completely different places depending on their mood at the time.
So I wanted to go there for sure at that time.
So I said, "I'll be with you.
I said, "I understand.
I want to know what to expect, but I also want you to decide what to expect.
Maybe we are similar.
I'd like to decide on the mood of the moment, or the feeling of the concert.
Next time, call Donki. When I met Yuzukinoko.
Hey, Donki. I wonder what I will say.
But Yuzuki-chan has always said she likes my face.
I'm saying it, I'm saying it.
That makes me so happy.
Don't you want her to hate you?
I don't want you to hate me.
You don't want me to hate you? I get it.
Yuzukichan. That's right.
When you call me "Yuzuki," I'm sure you'll be adored all the time, so don't worry.
I want to be adored.
We'll show each other the good things about our hometowns.
Food, nature, and so on.
Let's see...
That's not fair. It's Tohoku.
Ah.
Isn't it unfair? It's a big place.
Huh? Where are you, Makachan?
I'm in Fukushima.
Fukushima. Then, let's go to the good parts of Fukushima.
What are the good things about Fukushima?
Well, I don't know.
Let's see.
It is the closest to Kanto in Tohoku.
That's true.
Maybe only people in Fukushima think that.
People in Kanto probably think it's about the same.
But it's about an hour away.
Is Mt. Kobe in Fukushima?
Fukushima.
Is that close? Relatively.
It's closer, but Fukushima is farther away.
Fukushima because it's big.
I see.
So, I think it's good to call it a city because it's the closest.
I think Sendai is more urban. In fact.
But Fukushima, I have been there.
Hawaiians?
Yes, I have. I went to a live concert there.
But I want to go in there because they don't have a pool.
It's so much fun.
It was fun.
Have you done a few gigs?
And I wonder what the image is.
Ramen?
Northern ramen?
Peaches?
And history and castles.
Signals.
Yes, that's right.
Yes, for sure.
I want to go to Fukushima.
I'd love to.
I want to go.
I want you to go.
Hawaiians?
Okay, Hawaiian's first.
Taiwanese celebrations at the Hawaiians.
Wouldn't that be great?
Then, finish the concert in the morning and have fun in the afternoon.
It's great.
Just play normally.
That's what I like.
Let's all go to the water stage together.
I want to do that.
It looks like a lot of fun.
Doki will be on that side.
I'll probably act on my own.
What? Oh, no.
I'll do whatever I want to do.
Eh?
That's right.
If I change my clothes, I'll go with just the two of us, but that's what I want to do.
Three of us are there.
And one of us is doing makeup.
If there are three of us and two of us feel the same way, we go together, and one of us goes somewhere else.
We don't match.
It's amazing.
It's amazing, isn't it?
If it were us, the three of us would be together.
But we don't have that. That's the point.
But in a way, it might be necessary.But in a way, it may be necessary.
For TOKU, too.
On the contrary?
Oh, I see.
But there may come a time when it does.
Well, sure.
Someone will.
Right.
I see.
But I want them to be with me forever, though.
No longer.
Right?
It's been a long time.
It's been 7 years.
I think it's great that it's been 7 years.
I still want to stay in a big room with 9 people.
I definitely don't want to.
Once a year is fine. Once a year.
Once a year is too little.
But once a year, or when we go on a national tour, I would ask them to let us stay at a place like a ryokan (Japanese-style inn).
I told them to let me stay at a place with a big room and a hot spring.
It was amazing.
We do that, but only at that time.
I see.
Oh, let me tell you a good point about Aichi Prefecture.
What are the good things about Aichi Prefecture?
Well, the food.
I love it.
Really? Really?
Hitsu-mabushi ramen.
I really love it.
Many people don't like it because of its strong taste.
Heh~
I hear it's a little too rich.
Oh, I think it's just right.
Really? Good.
I wonder what else is left. Food.
And history. There are many warlords.
I love it.
Oh, I see. You like history, right?
I love history.
That's right.
I wonder what else.
Well, moderation is just fine.
I understand. Just right.
The place, you know. Yes, yes.
Because the place is just right.
I wonder.
It's the food, isn't it? I guess so.
The other day, we all went to Pork Road.
Seriously? Wasn't it delicious?
It's so good.
The second time.
Oh, I see.
Keep looking at the ceiling. The killer whale poster.
That's right.
I've been coming here for a long time.
It's delicious.
Just so you don't get jealous.
Why did you say that?
So that they'll be jealous.
I love it.
It's so good.
Super delicious.
Please go there every time you go to Nagoya.
I will meet you. I love it.
I love you. See you.
It's like he's asking me to close the door.
You got to talk.
You've never been nervous before, have you?
Today. I was wondering what to talk about.
When you first told me, I thought I was mistaken.
I know. Me too.
It's simple.
Me? I thought.
Something happened.
Did I do something? I thought.
I thought so. I thought, "Is there more to come? I thought, "What's going to happen in the future?
But you were able to talk to him. I'm glad.
I think we got to know each other better than Yuna.
Yay!
I'm having a great time.
Let's talk again.
It's nice to be in a local group.
I'm glad. I look forward to working with you as a localism.
Let's talk again.
Let's do it.
This is Nao Sakura, a member of the team staff.
Tomoko Inari, and Waka Yasumori.
Bye bye!